A Guide to the League of Women Voters of Virginia records, 1920-2011
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Subject files., Extent: 22 boxes. (Box 39-60)
  - Subseries 5: Legislature., 2 boxes (Box 45-46)
    - Legislature, 1986-1987. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Legislature, 1988-1989. (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Legislature, 1990. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Legislature, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Legislature, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Legislature, 1993-1994. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Legislature, 1995-1996. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Legislature, 1998-1999. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Legislature, 199[-]. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Legislature, 2000-2006. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Legislature, no date. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Legislative newsletters, 1962-1968. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Legislative newsletters, 1970-1971, 1974. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Legislative newsletters, 1980, 1989. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Legislative newsletters, 1992, 1994, 2004. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Delegation of power (folder 1 of 3). (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Delegation of power (folder 2 of 3). (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Delegation of power (folder 3 of 3). (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Dillon Rule study. (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 6: Government and Politics., 1 box (Box 47)
    - Blue Ribbon Strike Force, 1994. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Reports of congressional interviews, 1991-1995. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Intergovernmental relations, 1970, 1974-1975, 1979. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Home rule for D.C., 1962-1965. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Political parties, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Practical politics. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Citizens' Jury, 1992-1993. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 7: Campaign Financing., 1 box (Box 47)
    - Campaign financing--state and national, 1973-1976. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Campaign finance reform and public financing, 1988-1991, 1993, 1996. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Fair Campaign Study Commission, 1989. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Ethics pledge, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Campaign finance reform, 1999. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Campaign finance article, 26 June 2003. (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 8: Civil Rights., 2 boxes (Box 47-48)
    - Civil Rights, 1963-1965. (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Civil Rights, 1979, 1981-1984. (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Civil Rights, 1985. (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Civil Rights, 1986-1987. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 9: Taxation and Finance., 1 box (Box 48)
    - Taxation, 1950, 1954-1955, 1958, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Taxation, 1962-1963. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Taxation, 1964. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Taxation, 1965-1966. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Taxation and finances, 1975-1979. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Taxation and finances, 1981-1988. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Automatic Income Tax Reduction Act, 1951-1955. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Major Sources of Revenue for Arlington County, 1975. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - An Overview of State Government Finances in Virginia, 1976. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - New Directions in State and Local Tax Reform, 1977. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - The Role of the State in Local Finances, parts I and II, 1978. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - General Constitutional Limit on State Expenditures, 1981. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - General Revenue Sharing and the States. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Taxes: Who Pays? Who Should? (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Local Revenue Resources, 1995. (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 10: Women., 1 box (Box 49)
    - Status of women, 1964-1966. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Women, 1980-1986, 1994. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1973-1982, 2009. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Property rights, 1979, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Marital property rights, 1983-1984. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Property (divorce and death), 1979-1983. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Property rights (death), 1980-1982, 1984, 1988, no date. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Property rights (divorce). (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Dower and curtesy in divorce, 1988, 1995, no date. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Fault in divorce, 1984-1988. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Pay equity and comparable worth, 1982-1985. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Pay equity and comparable worth, 1986-1987, no date. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Government policy on reproductive choice, 1982-1995. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Public Policy on Reproductive Choices: A Balance of Rights (LWV-US) and Public Policy on Abortion (LWV-New Jersey). (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Pro-Choice Alliance, 1988, 1990-1991. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Planned Parenthood. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Women's Network, 1991-1993. (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 11: Children., 1 box (Box 50)
    - Children, 1964-1965, 1975, 1977, 198[-]. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Children, 1992-1997. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Child care, 1972-1974. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Child care, 1986-1987. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Child care study, August 1986. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Child care, 1988-1989. 198[-]. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Child care, 1990, 1992, 1994. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Child care, 1995-1997, no date. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Children at risk (abuse, poverty, crime, etc.), 1987. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Children at risk (abuse, poverty, crime, etc.), 1988, 198[-]. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Children at risk (abuse, poverty, crime, etc.), 1992, 1994-1997, no date. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Department for children, miscellaneous, 1988. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Council on Community Service for Youth and Families, 1990-1992. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Children's Action Network (CAN), 1994-1995. (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 12: Education., 2 boxes (Box 50-51)
    - Education, 1955-1958. (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Education, January-March 1959. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Education, April-September, no month 1959. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Education, 195[-]. (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Education, 1960-1967, 196[-]. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Education, 1973-1974, 1979. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Education, 1980-1985, 1988. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Education, 1990-1991. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Education, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Education, 1993. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Education, 1995-1996, 199[-]. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - National Committee for Support of the Public Schools, 1963-1965. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - School board elections, 1993-1994. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Elected school board questionnaires. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 13: Health., 1 box (Box 51)
    - Health care, 1979. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Health care, 1990. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Health care, 1991. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Health care, 1992-1993. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Smoking, 1982-1991. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Smoking (Waynesboro local league), 1986-1988. (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Breast Cancer Awareness Month, October 1996. (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 14: Mental Health., 2 boxes (Box 51-52)
    - Mental health, 1956-1959. (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Mental health, 1960-1965. (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Mental health, 1966-1968. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Mental health, 1985. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Mental health, January-November 1986. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Mental health, December 1986. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Mental health, January-April 1987. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Mental health, May-December 1987. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Mental health, January-March 1988. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Mental health, May-December, no month 1988. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Mental health, 1989. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Mental health, 198[-]. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - The Public Mental Health Care System in Virginia, 1986-1989. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 15: Welfare and Human Resources., 2 boxes (Box 52-53)
    - Welfare, 1956-1957. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Welfare, 1958-1960. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Welfare, 1961-1962. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Welfare, 1963-1965. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Poverty and welfare, 1967-1969, 1975, 1979, 1985. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Richmond Professional Institute, School of Social Work, 1965. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Human resources, 1963-1974, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Meeting Basic Human Needs, 1988-1989. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 16: System of Justice., 1 box (Box 53)
    - Consensus, 1974-1976. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1971, 1973-1976, 1980, 1982-1984, 1988-1989. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Study kits. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Printed materials. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Local leagues. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Kits, reports, speeches, addresses, presentations, conferences and workshops, and fact sheets. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Papers, 1973-1975, 1984. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 17: Adult Domestic Violence Study., 2 boxes (Box 53-54)
    - Drafts, reports (folder 1 of 2). (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Drafts, reports (folder 2 of 2). (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Consensus questionnaires. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Committee and volunteers. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Papers. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Legislation. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Agencies and organizations. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Printed and published materials. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 18: Property, Land Use, and Growth., 2 boxes (Box 54-55)
    - Vested property rights, 1989-1990, 1993. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Land use, 1972-1982. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Land use, 1983. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Land use, 1984-1986, 1990. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Land use resources. (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Housing and growth, 1968, 1970, 1973-1974. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Housing and growth, 1986-1987, 198[-]. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Housing and growth, 1990-1993, no date. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Growth Management Forum. (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Transferable Development Rights. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Housing Coalitions (Virginia Housing Coalition, Northern Virginia Housing Coalition), 1981, 1987-1992. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, 1988, 1991. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Redskins Stadium in Alexandria, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Disney's America theme park, 1994. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 19: Environment, 4 boxes (Box 55-58)
    - Waste, 1987-1989. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Hazardous waste, 1979-1981. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Hazardous waste, 1982. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Hazardous waste, 1983-1984. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Hazardous waste, 1985-1987, 198[-]. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Toxics Roundtable and Hazardous Waste Reduction: A New Direction for Virginia, 1987. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Study Transportation, Manufacture, and Storage of High Hazard Solids, Liquids, Gases, or Compounds, or Mixtures, Senate (Virginia) Document #32, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Hazardous waste, 1994-1995. (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Sewage and septic systems, 1981-1982. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Sewage and septic systems, 1983-1986, 1994, no date. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Solid waste, 1974-1975, 1982, 1985, 1987-1988. (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Air pollution and air quality, 1980-1989. (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Clean Air Act testimony by Merilyn B. Reeve, League of Women Voters-US, 22 March 1984. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Air pollution and air quality, 1990-1994. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Ambient Air Monitoring Data Report, Department of Environmental Quality Air Monitoring Section, 1993. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Air Quality and Enegery Policy in Virginia, Conservation Council of Virginia Conference, 26 September 1992. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Conservation Council of Virginia constitution. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Environmental quality, 1973-1985, 1989. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Environmental Network, 1994. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Energy, 1976-1983, 1987. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Energy newsletters, issues 1-2, 7-8, 11-12, 22-26, ca. 1981. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Clean Energy News, January 1995. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Recycling, 1988-1989. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Recycling, 1990, no date. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Beverage container legislation, 1974, 1981-1986. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Beverage container legislation, 1988, 1992. (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Natural resources, 1980-1990. (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Uranium, 1982-1986. (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Wildlife, 1993, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Water, 1956-1965. (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Water, 1966-1970. (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Water, 1980-1981. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Water, 1982. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Water, 1983. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Water, 1984-1989, 198[-], no date. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Water, 1991-1994. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - STEP (Service Training for Environmental Progress), 1990. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Blueprint for Clean Water. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Crosscurrents: The Water We Drink. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Virginia's Water Supply Problems: Searching for Solutions, 1982. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Virginia's Water Supply: A Reference Handbook, 1982. (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Water for Tomorrow: A Report on Water and Wastewater Needs in Virginia, Virginia Water Project, Inc. (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Back Bay, 1975-1976. (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Chesapeake Bay, 1979. (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Chesapeake Bay, 1980-1982. (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Chesapeake Bay, 1983-1988. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Chesapeake Bay, 1989. (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Chesapeake Bay, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Chesapeake Bay, 1991-1992. (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Chesapeake Bay, 1993-1994. (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Chesapeake Bay, no date. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Missouri River Basin: Water Policy for the Future. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Year of the Coast: correspondence, 1980-1981. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Year of the Coast: workshop materials. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Year of the Coast: workshop materials. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Coastweeks, 1986-1987. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Coastal preserves, 1991. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 20: International Relations, 2 boxes (Box 58-59)
    - Papers, 1962-1967. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Papers, 1979-1987. (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - National security, 1982-1986. (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - National security, 1987. (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - National security, 1988. (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - National security, 1989, 1991. (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Foreign trade, 1954, 1961-1965. (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Foreign trade, 1973-1983, 1987, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Foreign aid, 1957, 1963-1967. (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - China, 1966-1967. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - United Nations, 1954-1957, 1962-1965. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - United Nations, 1976, 1982, 1990. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 21: Future Horizons, 1 box (Box 59)
    - Future Horizons: Virginia in the Twenty-First Century. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Future Horizons: Virginia in the Twenty-First Century. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Future Horizons: Virginia in the Twenty-First Century (includes process guide). (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Future Horizons: Virginia in the Twenty-First Century(includes two copies and process guide). (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Future Horizons: Virginia in the Twenty-First Century summary of regional meetings and final document. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Future Horizons: Virginia in the Twenty-First Century related papers. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 22: Miscellaneous files, 2 boxes (Box 59-60)
    - Gun control, 1984, 1990-1993. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Labor unions, 1973-1976. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Labor unions, 1977-1990. (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Virginia trade. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Security, 1984. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - A Bicentennial Look at Virginia,1976. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Comparative fault. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - John Warner interview, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Virginia's Capitol, 2001-2005, no date. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Virginia's Executive Mansion, no date. (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Series V: Local Leagues., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 60-69)
  Local Leagues papers contains booklets, brochures, correspondence, lists, maps, minutes, newsletters, policies, position papers, publications, reports, rosters, studies, and other papers concerning the formation, organization and operation, and programs of various local leagues in Virginia, as well as information on local government and politics. In some instances, papers concern the disbandment of local leagues.
  - Subseries 1: Individual Local Leagues, 9 boxes (Box 60-68)
    - Alexandria: annual meetings, 1988, 1992. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Alexandria: bulletins, November 1989. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Alexandria: positions, 1987-1988. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Alexandria: study, 1985. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Alexandria: Know Your City. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Alexandria: member handbooks. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Alexandria: membership. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Alexandria: brochures. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Alleghany County: A Guide to Local Government. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Arlington: annual meetings, 1991,1993. (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Arlington: bulletins, April 1991, January, April 1996. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Arlington: Arlington Community Guide. (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Arlington: Solving the Budget Puzzle in Arlington. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Arlington: studies, 1989-1990. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Arlington: membership. (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Arlington: members handbook. (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Arlington: brochures. (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Arlington: papers. (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Charlotte Court House: correspondence, 1992. (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Charlottesville-Albemarle: annual meetings, 1986, 1990-1993. (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Charlottesville-Albemarle: Guide to Local Government, (2 copies of 1987 edition) 1980, 1987. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Charlottesville-Albemarle: Guide to Local Government, (2 copies), 1992. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Charlottesville-Albemarle: membership and directories. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Charlottesville-Albemarle: budget information, 1993-1994. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Charlottesville-Albemarle: brochures, local program. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake: by-laws. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake: annual meetings, 1977, 1982, 1984. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake: annual report questionnaire, 1982. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Chesapeake: correspondence, 1977, 1985. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake: membership directories/rosters, officers and board directories/rosters. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Clarke County: league organization papers. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Clarke County: by-laws. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Clarke County: meeting minutes, 1984 (organization), 1986-1987 (board). (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Clarke County: The Government of Clarke County (2 copies). (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Clarke County: correspondence, 1984, 1986. (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Clarke County: membership rosters. (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Clarke County: budgets, 1984-1987. (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Clarke County: disbandment, 1993. (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Culpeper: recognition request. (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Culpeper: by-laws. (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Culpeper: revised by-laws, 1995. (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Culpeper: Know Your Town and County (2 copies) and list of whom voters elect. (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Culpeper: board meeting minutes, 1991-1993. (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Culpeper: correspondence, 1990-1992. (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Culpeper: correspondence, 1993, 1995. (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Culpeper: reproductive rights forum. (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Culpeper: fifth anniversary. (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Culpeper: annual meeting, 24 June 1997. (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Culpeper: disbandment, 1990-1992. (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Culpeper: membership rosters, 1990-1993, 1996-1997. (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Culpeper: clippings. (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Danville: by-laws. (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Danville: annual report and annual meetings, 1977, 1984, 1986. (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Danville: board meeting minutes, 1979[?], 1984-1986. (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Danville: bulletins, 1969, 1979-1986. (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Danville: Know Your City and Facts for Voters. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Danville: correspondence, 1985-1989, 1992, no date. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Danville: board rosters and directories, membership rosters and directories, 1977-1989. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Danville: withdrawal of recognition. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax area: by-laws. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax area: Here We Stand positions and by-laws. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax area: annual meetings, 1977-1979, 1989, 1991-1992. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax area: board meeting minutes, 1984-1985. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax area: newsletter and bulletins, 1983, 1990-1991. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Fairfax area: position and correspondence, 1969-1970. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Fairfax area: correspondence, 1984-1991. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Fairfax area: studies, September 1973-September 1975. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Fairfax area: studies, October 1975-September 1976. (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Fairfax area: studies, October 1976-December 1977. (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Fairfax area: studies, January 1978-December 1979. (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Fairfax area: studies, 1988-1989. (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Fairfax area: reports. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax area: pamphlets and brochures including Facts for Voters. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Fairfax area: board of directors rosters and directories, membership rosters and directories, 1979, 1981-1982, 1991. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax area: members handbook. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax area: calendar, fund drive card, 1992-1993. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax area: board notebook contents. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax area: papers, 2003-2004. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Falls Church: annual meetings, 1987, 1989-1992. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Falls Church: positions, 1988, 1992. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Falls Church: studies. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Falls Church: policies of the board of directors. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Falls Church: membership list, 1992. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Falls Church: correspondence, 1991-1992. (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Falls Church: guide to voting brochures. (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Falls Church: clippings and newspapers. (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Fredericksburg: by-laws. (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Fredericksburg: reorganization efforts. (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Fredericksburg: minutes, 1952-1985. (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Fredericksburg: bulletins, 1981-1984. (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Fredericksburg: annual reports, 1980, 1982. (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Fredericksburg: Know Your Fredericksburg (2 copies), brochure. (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Fredericksburg: correspondence, 1950-1969. (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Fredericksburg: correspondence, 1970-1985, 1991-1992. (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Fredericksburg: board directories and rosters, membership directories and rosters, 1979-1984. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Fredericksburg: town meeting, 1 February 1955. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Fredericksburg: miscellaneous papers. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Gloucester-Mathews: recognition paperwork. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Gloucester-Mathews: correspondence, 1967-1971. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Gloucester-Mathews: handbook, 1983-1984. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Gloucester-Mathews: membership directories/rosters, 1969-1970, 1990-1991. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Gloucester-Mathews: disbandment, 1995-1996. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Hampton-Newport News: bulletin, 1993, 1996. (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Hampton-Newport News: position paper. (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Hampton-Newport News: A Citizen's Guide to Hampton City Government (2 copies). (Box 64, Folder 11)